1kuwaitjobs.com 2019-06-29

# Privacy Policy| 1 Kuwait Jobs

The privacy of our visitors is very important to us. This Privacy Policy will help you understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose personal information.

## Advertising Cookies

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads to users that visit **https://1kuwaitjobs.com**  
In some countries (except EU) Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve personalized ads to **1 Kuwait Jobs** users that are based on their previous website visits. Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

## Direct Data Submission via forms

Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. For example when you apply for a job, or post a job offer the information you provide will be collected and stored in our data base, cookies and other local storage mechanism.

1 Kuwait Jobs will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.

## Sharing

When posting a job offer on **1 Kuwait Jobs** the information you have submitted will be available publicly, and be searchable on **https://1kuwaitjobs.com** until you deactivate the job advert.

When applying for a job your information will be sent directly to the employer/company that advertised the job offer.

We will protect personal information stored on our servers by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

## Log Files

 **1 Kuwait Jobs** makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

On some pages, **1 Kuwait Jobs** does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

## Links

 **1 Kuwait Jobs** may contain links to other web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other web sites. We suggest our users to be aware of this when they leave **https://1kuwaitjobs.com** and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our website.
